interupload.com 2015-11-04

# Free Cloud Storage and Unlimited Access

### myVdrive Privacy Policy

#### Thank you for using myVdrive.com.

When you register on our Site, you hereby agree and acknowledge that your Personal Information will be placed into the myVdrive.com database and that such Personal Information shall be shared with third parties for marketing purposes.

#### Personal Information that We Collect from You

When you register on myVdrive.com, users allow us and our affiliates to make their Personal Information available to third parties, which are collected when submitting an application to become a member or using our Services.

These Personal Information includes, but are not limited to: a) email address; b) credit card information or PayPal® information (depending on how you made a payment); and/or c) any other information requested on the registration form.

#### Logging IP Addresses

For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server does not recognize any information regarding the domain or e-mail address. IP addresses are logged and used by myVdrive.com for measuring usage.

#### Certain Exceptional Disclosures

We may disclose your information if necessary to protect our legal rights or if the information relates to actual or threatened harmful conduct or potential threats to the physical safety of any person. Disclosure may be required by law or if we receive legal process.

#### Use of Cookies

myVdrive.com.com may use cookies to store the preferences of users.

#### File Transfer Security

We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site. All files stored for delivery are deleted when they have been uploaded to third-party websites.

#### Third Party Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

#### Third Party Cookies

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.
